Customize the exploration of a city. Free download.City Explorer is not a usual tourist guide. City Explorer was developed because users wish to experience cities in different ways. Tourists, architects, historians, children have different interests. Besides browsing information about places, City Explorer provides support for creating and editing places and itineraries in a city.This release contains an example database of relevant places for tourists visiting the city of Trondheim in Norway. You can add places and create itineraries as you wish using City Explorer. Other databases can also be downloaded from our web site. We provide a database of buildings in Trondheim illustrating some architectural styles and a database of sculptures in Trondheim.You can also create a database for exploration of your preferred places in any city you want, and share it. To create a database, either use City Explorer on Android or a SQLite editor tool on a desktop. We advice you to start the creation of your database from one of our databases that provide the proper database table structure.The code for City Explorer is available as open source on github. Visit our web site for more information.